Good morning guys. Welcome back to our
channel. So here I'm
sharing the two trades that I have taken
today and what was the setup and whether
we achieved our target or we achieved
like or the stop loss got hit. I'll
explain that. So first trade that I took
was in Bat Podge. So here the setup was
uh this
uh there was a slight gap up opening in
the bar and then the market came down
and here uh the 9:30 candle has taken
off the low of 9:15 candle.
So usually after this there should be
one more red candle on that setup I
usually trade. But here even though
there was no perfect trade I have
entered my trade here expecting it would
fall because even nifty was falling at
the same time. So expecting Nifty would
fall at the same time but that didn't
happen and my stop loss got triggered.
So if I talk about my entry, this was my
entry here
somewhere here somewhere. My entry was
there. Then my stop loss and target were
this take line. So stop loss was this
around like any candle that closes above
this candle would have been my stop loss
and the target was
this. But unfortunately
uh that never even came back my buying
price also even though there were few
chances like it would come back here
also it was not closing above but at the
end at around
115 with around 25% of loss I have to
book my loss
25% I have to give the trade the money
to the market so it was a good amount
like 4,000 approximately like 3,700 or
800 I have lost in this trade But the
only learning is here until setup is
properly there do not trade because this
is normal setup honestly like here I get
actually I get activated here but
followed by way there should be a red
candies only then I used to take the
trade but
here the homo the fear of missing
out kicked in and I lost the trade that
is fine and and and a learning so we
should not do
that. So fine, everything is fine in the
game. And then the next trade was in
ICIC longboard. Here it was interesting.
So it was a way gap down. So market
pulled it uh it came till the day high
and here it given the high like it broke
the 9:15 candle like day high was taken
off here and next candle if it was it
would have been a green candle I would
have taken the trade at C but it was a
red candle and I thought all the buyers
were trapped. So what I did I did so I
have entered the trade in this candle
itself uh here
itself somewhere here I have entered the
trade and with a very small stop loss I
went into this trade like uh my stop
loss was this uh like this candle's high
was my stop
loss this was my stop loss And my target
was some somewhere here. Here here
somewhere here.
But unfortunately what happened in the
next 5 minutes itself it just touched my
touched my stop loss and as soon as the
stop loss got hit uh I have booked the
loss but immediately the market turned
the other way and it was there was a
good fall like even though it didn't
touch my target but again it took off my
stop loss but yeah both the trades I
have lost but here I have lost very less
and But in co I have lost around 25% of
amount that I have been invested. So if
you have a look at my positions, so I
have lost 3,500
[Music]
in CO forge and 800
in IC. But I need to come to the orders.
So I have bought coge at 27 rupees and
sold it at 20 rupees and I have bought
IC longboard at 35 rupees and sold it at
32. The bad part of retail trains is
this one. I have bought it at 27 and
told it at 20. But now after the market
it is a 24.
So this happens and here I have booked
my profit in see India. So even though
it is in upper circuit in the morning it
was not in upper circuit. So I have put
some good amount here and overall if it
talk then 4,500 is the loss which is
good amount for small good amount
partial like I would say myself not a
complete trader but part-time trader so
it is a good amount for me loss but that
is the market we have to respect the
stop lo and going forward I will take
care of stop loss
and setups so that's it this video